Attention!
I shall now explain the
plan to retake Trost.
Let me introduce you to
Eren Jaeger, from the Trainee Corps.
He is the result of a top-secret project
to turn humans into Titans.
He will become a Titan,
pick up the giant boulder
by the shattered gate,
carry it over, and seal the hole.
Your job will be
to protect him from Titans
while he moves the boulder!
When this mission succeeds,
humanity will have retaken
its territory from them
for the very first time.
Compared to all that humanity has lost,
it may seem insignificant.
But for humanity,
that step will be a great advance in
our attack on the Titans!
Eren, don't you know who I am?
It's me, Mikasa!
Your family!
Move, Ackerman!
What the?
He's just like any other stupid Titan!
I'm changing the plan.
We protect Jaeger from the Titans
until we can retrieve him.
He's still valuable as one
of humanity's last hopes.
We cannot just abandon him like this.
Where am I?
I'm at home?
Jean!
Why isn't he using his Maneuver Gear?
No way... Is it broken?
I'll come up with something!
Mikasa!
What happened to the plan?
It failed.
Everyone's fighting because
we can't leave Eren.
But there are too many...
Before long, they'll wipe us out.
The spot on the back of the neck,
ten centimeters across and a meter high.
Eren... Answer me!
You knew that hell was one
step beyond the walls.
So why did you want to go?
Why?
Because I was born into this world!
Eren!
Primal Desires
The Battle for Trost (9)
Damn it...
Why am I the one slowing us down?
Can I really come up with something?
Captain, we're finished!
We're the last ones left!
Fall back to the boulder!
What's the situation?
Five Titans,
coming from the gate.
I can't wait till they're gone! No way!
Jean!
His Maneuver Gear really is busted.
What's wrong?
Crap...
What's wrong with it?
Damn it...
Not now!
Jean, calm down!
Marco?
What are you doing?
Jeez.
Don't be such a pain in the ass!
Damn, why is the trigger
so hard to pull?
Jean!
What are you doing?!
Look who's talking?
Hurry and get out of here!
You're insane!
You're the crazy one!
Can't believe I survived that...
Look at that.
Eren...
Mikasa!
Armin!
Eren won!
Now he's trying to get the job done!
If we can cover him till
he gets to the gate,
we win!
Defend him at all costs!
Protect Eren until he reaches the gate,
even if it costs you your life!
Don't let any of the Titans near him!
Don't let them interfere!
Protect Eren!
You two, head toward Eren.
That's an order!
Got it?
Roger!
Mitabi's squad...
What are they doing?
The Titans won't follow us!
We have to get closer to them
until they attack us!
Look over here, bastards!
If you don't, I'll jab my blade
up your stinking ass!
Here they come!
Two of them are coming!
Run!
Run to the building!
What the...
Going on the ground is suicide.
Without horses or buildings,
they can't fight!
No... Now, it's the only way left...
Follow Mitabi's squad!
Armin, let's go, too.
This way! Over here!
My body feels like it's being crushed...
Mikasa? Armin?
What are you doing?
If you stay down there,
Titans will get you!
Come on, you slowpokes!
Over here!
H-Hey!
Mitabi!
So why did you want to go to
the world beyond the walls?
From the time we are born,
we are free...
It doesn't matter how strong
those who would deny
us that freedom are...
Flaming water... Frozen earth...
I don't care what it is!
The one who sees them
will be the freest person in the world!
Fight...
I'd willingly give my life for that!
It doesn't matter how
terrifying the world is.
cruel the world is!
Fight...
Fight!
Another Titan?
I'll handle it.
Out of the way!
Go, Eren!
Fight!
Everyone...
You didn't die in vain...
Today, for the first time, humanity
has defeated the Titans!
Yellow smoke round sighted.
The operation has succeeded!
Send more reinforcements!
Evac the elite team!
Information We Can Share So Far:
History of the War Against the Titans (1)
The oldest available records say
the Titans appeared 107 years ago.
They devoured most of humanity.
Information We Can Share So Far:
History of the War Against the Titans (2)
Humanity retaliated with cannons,
but they were useless in the face
of the Titan's regenerative ability.
The rest of the Titans are coming!
Get up the walls!
We'll evacuate after we get Eren.
Armin?
How's Eren?
He's so hot, I can barely believe it!
We need to hurry up the walls...
Part of his body is
fusing with the Titan.
I can't pull him out!
We'll have to cut him out.
Wait!
Eren...
Armin!
Mikasa?
That's...
Wings of freedom...
Hey, brats.
What's going on here?
Afterwards, the sudden arrival and
assistance of the Survey Corps,
along with the efforts of
the Garrison's engineers,
allowed Wall Rose to withstand
the Titans once more.
It took a full day to eradicate the remaining
Titans now trapped within Trost.
The barrage of fixed canon fire
from atop the walls was endless.
HE rounds killed most of the
Titans swarming the walls.
The few surviving Titans were
primarily killed by the Survey Corps.
During that operation, humanity managed
to take one 4-meter class and
one 7-meter class alive.
However,
207 were dead or missing,
and 897 were wounded.
Humanity had indeed scored its
first victory against the Titans,
but there were too many casualties
for anyone to celebrate.
Hey...
You're...
Marco...?
Trainee,
do you know his name?
I knew I hadn't seen him around...
But this couldn't have
happened to him...
Marco,
what happened?
D-Did anyone...
Did anyone see how he died?
What's his name?
If you know, tell me now.
Do you understand, trainee?
It's already been two days
since the hole was sealed.
And we still haven't finished
collecting the bodies.
At this rate, there
could be an epidemic.
We must avert a second tragedy.
There isn't time to
mourn your friend yet.
Understand?
104th Trainee Corps.
Captain of Squad 19, Marco Bott.
Marco, then?
I'm glad we have a name.
Let's get back to work.
What is this?
Where a Titan threw up.
They don't have digestive organs.
So after they've eaten all they can,
they throw up like that...
That's so...
Damn...
There's no way to identify anyone in this!
I'm sorry...
I'm sorry.
Apologizing won't help.
Just mourn his passing.
Any questions?
The leader of the Survey Corps
strike force, Commander Erwin.
And Captain Levi...
U-Um...
Where
am I?
As you can see, it's an
underground jail cell.
The Military Police has
retained custody of you.
We only recently received permission
to speak with you.
That key...
Yes.
It's yours.
You can have it back later.
The basement of your house
in Zhiganshina, Doctor Jaeger's house,
holds the answer
to the mystery of the Titans.
Is that it?
Yes...
I think so.
That's what my father said.
You have amnesia, and
your dad's missing.
Pretty convenient.
Levi.
We already reached the conclusion
that he has no reason to lie.
There's still so much we don't know.
But right now, we need to
ask what you want to do.
What I want to do?
To get to your house,
we must retake Zhiganshina
and Wall Maria.
The simplest and easiest way
to seal the shattered gate
would be to use your Titan power.
It's likely that Titans
will determine our fate.
The Colossal Titan and the Armored Titan
are the same, in principle, as you.
Your decision is the key.
The key that can save
humanity from despair.
I...
I am?
I'll kill them all!
I'll wipe every last Titan
off the face of this Earth!
Answer up, you piece of crap.
What do you want to do?
I want to join the Survey Corps
and just slaughter the Titans!
Oh?
Not bad.
Erwin,
I'll take responsibility for him.
Convey that to the brass.
It isn't that I trust him.
If he betrays us or loses control,
I'll kill him on the spot.
They shouldn't complain.
Because only I can do it.
I accept your request.
You can join the Survey Corps.
A promise held high.
A hope trampled.
A rage festering deep within.
In a confused haze,
Eren hallucinates about
all that has happened since that day.
Since That Day